<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>Venture Harbour Engineering Blog</title>
        <link>https://ventureharbour.tech/blog</link>
        <description>Venture Harbour Engineering Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[👋 Hello World]]></title>
            <link>https://ventureharbour.tech/blog/hello-world</link>
            <guid>hello-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Welcome to the world of Venture Harbour Engineering!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>It seems to be a tradition</strong> that every blog I start I start with a well wishing <em>hello world</em> post. So here I am, saying it again, <em>hello world</em>. This time I have the might of the entire Ventureneering team behind me and we have a lot to share, both to one another and the rest of the wider community. So welcome, I'm really glad you came along ❤️.</p><h4 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_mojV" id="questions">Questions?<a class="hash-link" href="#questions" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h4><h5 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_mojV" id="how-will-this-be-different-to-ventureharbourcom">How will this be different to ventureharbour.com?<a class="hash-link" href="#how-will-this-be-different-to-ventureharbourcom" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h5><p>So we are eager to get more mass appeal content from the engineers on the main site, and really this can act as the catalyst and breeding ground for that content. Not that content has to be editorially more or less significant. It's just tonally and demographically the main blog is very different, so this is a place without borders - albeit I hope we would all embody the Venture Harbour spirit! We can also experiment with interactive content a lot easier on this site, with <a href="https://docusaurus.io/docs/markdown-features/react" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Docusaurus allowing MDX content</a> you can embed experiments directly into the page!</p><h5 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_mojV" id="how-do-i-get-stuff-on-here">How do I get stuff on here?<a class="hash-link" href="#how-do-i-get-stuff-on-here" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h5><p>The <a href="https://github.com/ventureharbour/ventureneering" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">repository exists publicly</a> so internal or external collaborators can submit PRs and we would be delighted to review them. <a href="https://docusaurus.io/docs/blog#adding-posts" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Check out the Docusaurus docs</a> if you are having issues, we can always help get things looking just right if you struggle, so just open issues on our repo if you can't get something working.</p><h5 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_mojV" id="what-can-i-write-about">What can I write about?<a class="hash-link" href="#what-can-i-write-about" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h5><p>Anything you think is interesting. It's a great place to share <em>links</em> to interesting articles, <em>libraries</em> or <em>tech</em> that you find whilst journeying through your life as a developer. You can also <em>teach</em> us something, or give us a <em>TIL</em> (today I learned) - short posts are totally totally fine, it doesn't need to be epic, but it can also be epic!!</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>hello</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>